(Sheldon:)you should know that fanning
yourself in a humid environment
(Sheldon:)only raises
your body temperature.
(Rajj:)Huh. That does explain why
the servants used to look so hot
(Rajj:)while they were fanning me.
(Rajj:)Let's get our minds off
how uncomfortable we are.
(Rajj:)We could take some more
simulated instrument readings.
(Sheldon:)My major focus
(Sheldon:)at the moment is keeping
my claustrophobia at bay.
(Raj:)How's that going?
You tell me.
(Sheldon:)I feel like I can't breathe,
(Sheldon:)and I am tempted
to crack you open
(Sheldon:)and suck the air
right out of your lungs.
(Raj:)Sheldon, if this is
too much, we can stop.
(Sheldon:)We're not stopping.
(Leonard:)You don't have to
bite my head off.
(Sheldon:)I apologize.
(Penny:)I j...
(Sheldon:)I'm plagued
by an internal struggle.
(Raj:)If you would just use
the bucket,
(Raj:)you'd be
so much more comfortable.
(Sheldon:)My struggle is emotional.
(Raj:)Oh. Is it Amy?
(Sheldon:)It's dark matter.
(Sheldon:)When I entered
the field
(Sheldon:)of string theory,
I was a prodigy.
(Sheldon:)I rose to a position of respect,